<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industry News on Herfom</title>
    <link>https://www.herfom.com/category/industry-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industry News on Herfom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 14:42:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.herfom.com/category/industry-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and Development of Bopp Pressure Sensitive Adhesive Tape</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/characteristics-and-development-of-bopp-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:59:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/characteristics-and-development-of-bopp-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape/</guid>
      <description>Pressure-sensitive adhesive tapes were mass-produced in my country in the early 1980s. Water-emulsion acrylate pressure-sensitive adhesives were widely used in the production of BOPP packaging tapes. There are more than ten sets of cross-linking systems in the country with a scale of 0.5-15,000 T/year. Emulsion-type acrylate pressure-sensitive adhesive tape is the most productive and widely used variety of pressure-sensitive adhesive tapes. It has the incomparable advantages of traditional solvent-based pressure-sensitive adhesives: Good viscosity, safe use and good aging resistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOPP Pressure Sensitive Adhesive Tape Pressure Sensitive Adhesive Tape and Its Packaging Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/bopp-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape-and-its-packaging-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:55:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/bopp-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape-pressure-sensitive-adhesive-tape-and-its-packaging-applications/</guid>
      <description>Pressure-sensitive adhesive tape (PSAT: Pressure-sensitive Adhesive Tape) can be divided into rubber-type pressure-sensitive tape, thermoplastic elastomer pressure-sensitive tape, polyacrylate pressure-sensitive tape, polyvinyl ether pressure-sensitive tape and organic pressure-sensitive tape according to the main component. Silicone pressure-sensitive tape, etc., among which acrylate pressure-sensitive adhesive is the focus of current research and development. In terms of form, it is divided into solvent-type pressure-sensitive tape, emulsion-type pressure-sensitive tape, hot-melt pressure-sensitive tape and radiation-curing pressure-sensitive tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion on the Steel Belt Installation of Explosion Proof Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/discussion-on-the-steel-belt-installation-of-explosion-proof-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 10:01:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/discussion-on-the-steel-belt-installation-of-explosion-proof-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ​	In the construction of many chemical plants at home and abroad, there will be contact with the installation of a large number of explosion-proof electrical equipment, especially in petrochemical enterprises with many fields, due to the harsh environment, more and more armored cables are used for power transmission and distribution control. It is required to be grounded at both ends of the armored cable, so generally, the power distribution box on site, the inlet of the motor, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effects Of Moisture On Nylon Cable Ties</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/the-effects-of-moisture-on-nylon-cable-ties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 20:49:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/the-effects-of-moisture-on-nylon-cable-ties/</guid>
      <description>​	Nylon is a hygroscopic material, and as such is affected by variations in moisture levels.
​	For peak performance and for the as designed and tested conditions nylon should be stored at a controlled 73℉ and at 50% Relative Humidity. This storage results in a moisture conditioning of the nylon of 2.5%. While one realizes the realistic limitation of these conditions, nevertheless these are the optimum as designed and tested conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
