<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metal Cable Gland on Herfom</title>
    <link>https://www.herfom.com/category/metal-cable-gland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metal Cable Gland on Herfom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 11:23:33 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.herfom.com/category/metal-cable-gland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Air Vent Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/air-vent-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 09:04:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/air-vent-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: Nickel Plated Brass Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: -40℃ to 100℃ Feature: Waterproof and breathable, Balance pressure Support non-standard customization  Specification 1.Metric    Thread Item No. Cable Range Φ (mm) Thread O.D (mm) Thread Length (mm) Spanner Size (mm)     Other Size Please contact sales       M8x1.25 CGS-AIR-M8-4 2-4 8 5 11/11   M10x1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/brass-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 15:05:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/brass-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: Nickel Plated Brass Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: Static -40℃ to 100℃, or can heat up to 120℃ instantly. (Can be customized from -60℃ to 220℃) Product Features: Special clamping jaw and clamping ring design, large clamping cable range, strong tensile strength, waterproof, dustproof, salt-resistant, weak acid, alcohol, grease and general solvents Support non-standard customization  Structure   Parts A, C, and F are made of nickel-plated brass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMC Antimagnetic Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/emc-antimagnetic-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 09:19:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/emc-antimagnetic-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: Nickel Plated Brass Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: Static -40℃ to 100℃, or can heat up to 120℃ instantly. (Can be customized from -60℃ to 220℃) Product Features: This product is specially designed to treat the metal cable fixing head as an end body. When the isolated cable enters the fixing head, the copper contact piece attached in the fixing head can be used to contact the metal in the cable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porous Multiple Holes Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/porous-multiple-holes-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 09:50:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/porous-multiple-holes-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: Brass / Stainless Steel Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: Static -40℃ to 100℃, or can heat up to 120℃ instantly. (Can be customized from -60℃ to 220℃) Product Features: Special clamping jaw and clamping ring design, large clamping cable range, strong tensile strength, waterproof, dustproof, salt-resistant, weak acid, alcohol, grease and general solvents Support non-standard customization  Structure   Parts A, C, and F are made of Nickel-plated brass / Stainless Steel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silicone Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/silicone-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 21:17:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/silicone-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: The main part of the cable gland is made of brass nickel plating. The clamping parts and sealing parts are made of silica gel. Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: -50℃~+250℃ Support non-standard customization.  Specification 1.Metric    Thread Item No. Cable Range Φ (mm) Thread O.D (mm) Panel Mounting Hole (mm) Thread Length (mm) Joint Length (mm) Spanner Size (mm)     Other Size Please contact sales         M8x1 CGS-SIL-M8 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stainless Steel Cable Gland</title>
      <link>https://www.herfom.com/post/stainless-steel-cable-gland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 09:55:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.herfom.com/post/stainless-steel-cable-gland/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Thread Specifications: M (Metric), PG, G (PF), NPT Material: Stainless steel 304/316 Protection Level: IP68 Working Temperature: Static -40℃ to 100℃, or can heat up to 120℃ instantly. (Can be customized from -60℃ to 220℃) Product Features: Special clamping jaw and clamping ring design, large clamping cable range, strong tensile strength, waterproof, dustproof, salt-resistant, weak acid, alcohol, grease and general solvents Support non-standard customization  Structure   Parts A, C, and F are made of stainless steel 304/316.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
